Guide to the Scott Hubbard Papers SC1286
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2017-249
  - SFI Position Description (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Mars Pix (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - FBC (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Dep Div Chief Position (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Promotion Pkg GS (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Reorganization New Business, 1990 Feb (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Lumar Follow Up (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - K. Kimel Kentucky (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - LP Pix (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - GSH Fy 95 Fey Plan (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - GSH Fy92 Perf Appraisal (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Fy93 PA (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - SSE (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - FY 92 Perf Plan (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - "Pioneer" Approach (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - HQ Cost Data "Wernu Guuhel Others" (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - PutHoff (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Zero Point (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - IAF Logistics (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - IAF Paper (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - IAF 2001 Pres. Slides (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - IAF Paper (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Discovery, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Discovery, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Discovery - All years (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Discovery Debriefs Fy97 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - NAC @ JSC, Dec 1-3 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - NAC - All Cmts, Jul 27-31 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - NAC, 2015 Apr 8-10 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - NAC, 2015 Jan 13-16 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - NAC Tennis Dec Cancelled, 2014 Dec (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - NAC, 2014 Jul 28 - Aug 1 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - NAC, 2014 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - NAC 2014 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - OOTW Justin (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - CAIB (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - GAO, 2015 Mar 16 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Honda, 42822 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - KNTV, 2015 Jan 12 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Startalk, 2015 Jan 23 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Carmel Talk, 2015 Sep 25-27 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - KQED (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - WSJ-Vision (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - DNV-Top Tech, 2015 Sep 19 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - UCB Maersk, 2014 Oct 23 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Haas-Isaacs, 2014 Jun 30 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Top 500 Poland, 2013 Nov 19 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Top 500 - Poland UCB Stanford (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Maersk - Haas, 2013 Nov 01 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - DNV - Haas, 2013 Sep 18 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Maersk UCB, 43031 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - UCB Haas BNL, 2012 Oct 9 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - DNV Top Tech Haas, 2012 Sep 26 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - UCB Haas EETD, 2012 Jun 30 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - UCB Haas DNV Top Tech, 2012 Jan 24 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - UCB - Haas - BNL, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Haas Maersk, 2011 Oct 27 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - UCB Haas DNV Top Tech, 2011 Jan (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Haas/ LBUL Talk, 43018 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - AIAA Fellow Nomination, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Director's Round Table (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - UCB / LBUL, 2010 Nov 16 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Haas / UCB - DNV, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - UCB / Haas / DNV Lecture (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Haas Talk - Bus - Shool - DNV, 2008 Sep (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Lunar X-Paige (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Odyssey Moon (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Awards (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Idea Fest Space, 2014 Oct 4 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - IAA/IAC, 2015 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - IAC 2014 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - IAA; DC, 2014 Jan 9-10 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - China Tours (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - IAC / KY Trip, 2014 Sep 27-Oct 5 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - IAC, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - IAC Napoli, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - IAC, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Space San Diego, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - IAF Technical Comm (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - NSS, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Space San Diego, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - Space, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - IAC, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - GEN'L Atomics (Box 29, Folder 48)
  - Space Found Co Springs Coalition for Space (Box 29, Folder 49)
  - PI Forum, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  - LMATC - NDA - DARPA F6 (Box 29, Folder 51)
  - DARPA F6 BAA (Box 29, Folder 52)
  - Metis - F6 Econometrics (Box 29, Folder 53)
  - Metls F6 Kickoff M+9 (Box 29, Folder 54)
  - LMCO (Box 29, Folder 55)
  - LMATC - F6 (Box 29, Folder 56)
  - Space Dev (Box 29, Folder 57)
  - ExV - Media - After (Box 29, Folder 58)
  - Ex V-Workshop Final Docs (Box 29, Folder 59)
  - Exploration Workshops (Box 29, Folder 60)
  - KY-May, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Synthetic Life, 2007 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Tri-Fold (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - CISAC, 2006-2007 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - PA (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Stellar Solutions (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - BRITS (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Rovsing, 2007 Aug 10 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Rousing (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Rousing USA (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Rad Protect Sharp, 1989 Nov 9 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - IPP - Radiation Protection, 1990 March (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Radiation Background (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Radiation Protection (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - IEEE / Aerospace Papers Colorado, 1998 Mar 21-28 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Final IEEE/NSS Papers, 1997 Nov (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - IEEEE/NSS Dara, 1994 Nov (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Si(Li) NSS, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - TNS Final Review, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - IEEE NSS Papers Norfolk, 1994 Oct 30 - Nov 5 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - NSS Conf Record Papers, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - IEEE - NSS Si(Li), 1991 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - IEEE - Nss Si(Li) Background Comments (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - IEEE / NSS Si(Li) Final Draft Conference Record (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Monte Carlo Summary Si(Li) (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - IEEE / NSS Orlando, 1992 Oct (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - IEEE / NSS Abstract Submitted (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Innoative in Workshops, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Planetary Instrm Cost Workshoip (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Planetary Flight Instr Workshop, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - NSS / SiLi Paper - Final Version, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - NSS Si(Li) Paper, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Trans on Nucl Sci Si(Li) X-det Paper, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - COSPAR, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - SETI Benefactors (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - CISCO Space (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Space, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Ky Sat (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Vandy (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Rappaoit/Dyson (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - AIAA Paper on Space Entieps (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - JPL / SI Cakk Aboration (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - CSC Planning (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Stanford LLNL SI-Biodets (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - AB Sofia (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Univ. of Alabama - Humtsville (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - IPPW-5 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - AMES CD Forum, 2008 Sep 16 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - XPRIZE GALA, 43026 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - JDEM / SNAP (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - NASA FY, 2011 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - AIAA Space, 2011 Sep 27-29 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - NASA Bills, 2011-2011 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - OCT Proposals (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - FBC, 2010 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Shuttle Documentary (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - ISS NAT Lab (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Future Business (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Outer Planets Tech AIAA Space, 2009 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Clearance (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - SETI Background (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - SETI Actions, 2006 Mar (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - C (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - IAF - Bremen, 2003 Oct (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - IAC Paper B3 2008 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Space Invest Summit (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Emerging Entrep Space (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Master's Forums (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - SEOUL Dig Forum, 2008 May (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Seoul Music (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Drobes "R" Us (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Raytheon (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Donald Graham (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - CCST, 2007-2008 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - CASSE Report (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - CASSE - NRC Mars Epilog (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - CASSE NRC Final (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Stanford CSSPEX Plans (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - NASA, 2007-2008 (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - SETI / CSC, 2007-2008 (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - RV Practice Sessions, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - 105 Advanced Training (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - PMT Experiment II, 1985 Jun (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Photomultiplies Experiment Notes and Background, 1984 Jun - 1985 Mar (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Introduction to Remote Viewing (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - 177 RV (Cont'd) (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - 177 Advanced Training (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Crystal Data 296-445, 1982 Aug - 1983 Jun (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Crystal Profiles 597 to 747, 1984 Apr 16 - 1985 Feb 8 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Crystal Profiles 446 to 596, 1983 Jun - 1984 April (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Crystal Data 1-144, 1980 Mar to 1981 Oct (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Crystal Data 145-295, 1981 Oct - 1982 Aug (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Canberra Semiconductor, Inc. Progress Report (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Orren Tench Vol. 2 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - O. Tench (Vol 3) (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Profiles of Crystals Shipped (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Orren Tench (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Notes on Germanium Technology (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Canberra Visit, 1984 Oct (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Combined Data Sheets Crystal Growing ZRB (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Complete Detector Data Sheets (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - w/Okeefe, 2003 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Congrats (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Letters II Invites (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Vistors Center (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Ames CD (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Cheyenne Mountain Complex Photo (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Official Photo w/disk (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Letters Invitations (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, leters, etc (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Prx - Boffy, Earle, Bigelow (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - JPL Mars (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Letters Invites III (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Letters Corresp. (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - HRH Charles (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Honors Causa (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Letters, News (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - UARC (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Google (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Ames CD (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - IAC / KCBS Interview (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Astrogram (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - NASA Phone Books (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Post Ames (Box 37, Folder 24)